Oh, phew!
天
I thought we were in real trouble there for a second.
我还以为大难临头了呢
You scared us, you cute little guy.
你吓了我们一跳  可爱的小家伙
Boop.
砰
I shouldn't have booped his cute little nose.
我不该碰他的可爱的小鼻子
Don't call me cute!
别说我可爱
The boop was too much.
碰你很不应该
This is my city. You are on my turf.
这是我的城市  你们在我的地盘上
How can someone so cute be so violent?
这么可爱的小家伙怎么会这么凶
Ow!
啊
I said, don't call me cute!
我说了别说我可爱
Got it.
知道了
My name is Mr. Feng.
我是冯先生
I was cursed with these big, adorable eyes, and this fuzzy little body,
我摊上了这可爱的大眼睛和这毛绒绒的小身体
but make no mistake...
但别搞错了
I'm a weapon of mouse destruction.
我可是毁灭性的武器
Witness the power of my one-sixteenth-of-an-inch punch.
见识下我1/16英寸的拳头的厉害
Aw, that's cute.
真可爱